<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Events | PsyConnect</title><link>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/</link><atom:link href="https://psyconnect.github.io/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Recent &amp; Upcoming Events</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 14:45:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://psyconnect.github.io/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Events</title><link>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/</link></image><item><title>PsyConnect Plays!</title><link>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/mosanco-psyconnect-plays/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/mosanco-psyconnect-plays/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ever since the pandemic started, we have been hosting our “PsyConnect Plays!” on Zoom. Fortunately, with the recent loosening of Covid-19 measures, we were finally able to hold our first ever board games edition of “PsyConnect Plays!” on-site at Settler’s cafe on the 19th December 2021.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Of course, with the Covid-19 protocols in place so as to ensure the safety of everyone even as we have fun! What a jolly way to start this Christmas season with many new faces and exchanges of laughter!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PsyConnect Movie Screening - Starred Up</title><link>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/starred-up-psyconnect-movie/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 14:45:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://psyconnect.github.io/event/starred-up-psyconnect-movie/</guid><description>&lt;p>We were thankful to have A/P Timothy Leo (from our Master’s in Forensic Psychology programme) join us to review the movie “Starred Up” through the lenses of a Psychologist in a Forensic setting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Starred Up” is a prison crime drama film based in London. It revolves around the life of a young offender who got transferred into an adult prison prematurely. The film explores the challenges in rehabilitation work with violent offenders struggling with dysfunctional parent-child relationships as well as the effects of Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACE).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After the movie, A/P Timothy Leo shared with us his experiences gleaned over the many years of working with offenders locally and abroad. Throughout the session, students were able to clarify doubts and raise questions during the Q&amp;amp;A session. At the end of the event, our students learned more about psychological work in the forensic setting.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>